<resources>
    <string name="message_high_score">Congratulations, you got a high score !</string>

    <string name="message_game_end_new_game">Current game is up! Will you like to start a new game ?</string>
    <string name="message_custom_board">Tap on empty holes to pace a peg. Tap
    the lock button when complete</string>
    <string name="message_custom_board_done">Custom board is setup, you can start playing.
    Note that high scores for custom boards are not recorded</string>
    <string name="message_intro_first">
        Move a peg to an available hole in a straight line jumping over another peg
    </string>
    <string name="message_intro_second">The peg jumped over is removed</string>
    <string name="message_intro_third">Try to remove as many pegs as possible</string>
    <string name="message_intro_fourth">Getting only 1 peg remaining is the goal</string>
    <string name="message_board_reset_confirm">This will cancel the current board. Do you want to proceed ?</string>
    <string name="message_game_over">No more moves are possible. Game is up !</string>
    <string name="message_solver_complete">Solver has computed the moves
    that lead to a minimum number of pegs.\n\nUse the Forward button to see the board moves.</string>
    <string name="message_solver_complete_free">Solver has computed the moves
    that lead to a minimum number of pegs. Since this is a free version,
    the solver can find a solution leading to a minimum of 3 pegs only. In the paid version
    the solver can find a solution with 1 peg.\n\nUse the Forward button to see the board moves.
    </string>
    <string name="message_solver_complete_title">Found solution with pegs: </string>
    <string name="message_solver_inprogress_title">Searching for solution ...</string>
    <string name="message_solver_inprogress">Current lowest peg count: </string>

    <string name="message_solver_start_confirm">Depending on the current board, the Solver may take
    a few seconds to several minutes in computing a solution with least number of pegs.
    Since the Solver does a lot of computations, it will deplete battery power.
        It is advised that you put your phone on charge before starting the solver.
    While running the Solver can be stopped at any time and latest peg result
        will be available.</string>
    <string name="message_solver_mode_play_board">
        Cannot play game in solver mode. Select New Game to start a new game</string>

    <string name="message_confirm_switch_from_standard">
        Current board is set to Standard, do you want to change to French board ?</string>
    <string name="message_confirm_switch_from_French">
        Current board is set to French, do you want to change to Standard board ?</string>
</resources>
